He will destroy the world. No man can stop him. No
man will even try. He is The Chosen.
Holocaust 2000 is a science fiction, drama, horror
film directed by Alberto De Martino.
An executive in charge of a nuclear power plant in the Mid-East must stop his
son-- who turns out to be the Anti Christ -- from blowing it up.
Robert Caine, played by Kirk Douglas.
Sara Golan, played by Agostina Belli.
Angel Caine, played by Simon Ward.
Professor Griffith, played by Anthony Quayle.
Dr. Kerouac, played by Adolfo Celi.
Charrier, played by Romolo Valli.
Holocaust 2000 (also released as The Chosen and Rain of Fire) is a 1977 horror film directed by Alberto De Martino, written by De Martino, Michael
Robson, and Sergio Donati, and starring Kirk Douglas, Simon Ward, Agostina Belli, Anthony Quayle, Virginia McKenna, and Alexander Knox.
The original musical score was composed by Ennio Morricone.
The British-Italian co-production was produced by Edmondo Amati for The Rank Organisation and Titanus, and is
widely-considered a cash-in on the success of the similarly-themed The Omen, which was released a year earlier.
It received mixed reviews, but has become a cult classic.
The film explores themes of nuclear power plant, nuclear holocaust, armageddon.
The tone is dark and emotional and thought_provoking.